关于成功和失败的说明。
A note on success and failure.
美国职棒大联盟
Major League Baseball.
那些付出了数百万美元的人花了整整一百万美元
People that get paid millions and millions
of dollars to spend literally their entire
做一件事，一般是用球棒打个球。
lives training to do one thing, and
it's generally to hit a ball with a bat.
那是不熟悉的美式棒球
That's American baseball for
those not familiar.
此值为 0.300 ，这是一个好的平均批处理数。
This 0.300,
this is considered a good batting average.
这实际上被认为是一个极佳的击球平均。
This actually considered
an excellent batting average.
这意味着每当你站在球棒上的时候
This means that every time that you
step up to bat, swing that ball,
你有三个尝试，或者四，五个，这不重要。
you have three tries, or
four or five, it doesn't matter.
每次你去打就会有七次你会错过的
Every time you go up to hit,
seven out of ten times you're gonna miss.
所以大部分时间你都会失败的
So you're gonna fail most of the time.
但如果你成功地完成了这十次
But if you succeed three
out of those ten times,
你被认为是个非常好的保姆
you're considered a very good hitter.
你被认为是优秀的
You're considered excellent.
很棒的球员，你可能获得了数百万美元的报酬。
Excellent player, you're probably getting
paid millions and millions of dollars.
所以我想做的是重新思考失败的想法
So what I wanna do is reframe
thinking about failure,
因为那里有胜利还有学习
because there's winning and
then there's learning.
Cuz ，您始终可以从失败中学习。
Cuz you can always learn
from your failures.
我想做的就是把我们弄到 0 .
Really what I wanna do is get us at 0.500.
这意味着每两次访谈中就有一个你会成功的
That means about one out of every two
interviews, you're gonna succeed,
太神奇了
which is amazing.
听起来像是失败
It sounds like failure.
在你被拒绝和拒绝的时候
And at the time's where you're
getting rejected and rejected,
你在想面试很困难我是个失败人
you're thinking,
interviewing's hard, I'm a failure.
我不是一个好工程师
I'm not a good engineer.
也许我不够聪明
Maybe I'm not smart enough.
但如果我能把你搞到一半
But if I can get you to half,
就像你在面试中的一半一样你做得太棒了
as in you pass half your interviews,
you are doing phenomenal.
我和很多人谈过，没有人这样做。
And I talked to a lot of people,
nobody's at this.
我不认识一个能每两次面试一次的人
I don't know a single person that can
pass one out every two interviews.
聪明的人也是
Smart people, too.
你听说过的人
People that you've heard of.
那些有图书馆的人
People that have written libraries.
人们改变了我们对 JavaScript的看法
People that have changed the way
we think about JavaScript,
他们无法通过两次访谈中的一个
they couldn't pass one
out of two interviews.
我想让我们作为一个社区，作为一个文化。
I'd like to get us there,
as a community, as a culture.
我想让你到 0 .
And I wanna get you to 0.501.
所以我想让你略好一点
So I wanna get you slightly better
than half, cuz that's pretty good.
今天我们要完成采访的步骤
Today we're gonna go through
the steps of an interview.
我们要从申请开始
We're gonna start with the application.
我们会和招聘人员或招聘经理进行初步通话。
We're gonna go into that initial call
with the recruiter or the hiring manager.
我们要去做密码测试
We're gonna go into the code tests.
然后我们要谈电话屏幕
And then we're gonna talk
about the phone screen.
然后我们就去现场吃点肉
Then we're gonna get to the onsite,
kind of the meat and
如果你愿意去面试
potatoes, if you will, of interviewing.
然后我们要谈谈结果如何交易成功
And then we're gonna talk about
the results, how to deal success,
如何处理失败的问题。
how to deal with failure.
如果你是说杰姆我们为什么不能直接跳到现场
And if you're saying Jem, why can we just
skip straight to the on-site part cuz
我在乎的那部分吗
that's the part that I care about?
我有个坏消息要给你
I got some bad news for you.
从统计角度来说，大多数人永远不会到达现场。
Statistically speaking,
most of you will never get to the on-site.
这只是个数字游戏
That's just a numbers game.
我想说很多大公司
I would say a lot of the big companies,
他们大概会雇佣 10% 的人申请
they probably hire maybe 10%
of the people that apply.
比这些大公司更容易进入斯坦福或哈佛
It's easier to get into Stanford or
Harvard than some of these big companies,
就会有更多的人来
just by running the numbers.
所以我想谈谈到现场的步骤。
So I wanna talk about the steps
to get to the on-site.
然后我们会处理很多你可能得到的问题
And then we're gonna cover a lot of
the questions that you might get, or
你要问的问题的风格
the style of questions you're gonna get.
[ 空白音频]
[BLANK AUDIO]